{
  "id": "013-time",
  "title": "Time & Dates",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "šiandien",
      "choices": [
        "today",
        "tomorrow",
        "yesterday",
        "now"
      ],
      "answer": "today",
      "tts": "šiandien"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "rytoj",
      "choices": [
        "tomorrow",
        "today",
        "later",
        "yesterday"
      ],
      "answer": "tomorrow",
      "tts": "rytoj"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "vakar",
      "choices": [
        "yesterday",
        "today",
        "now",
        "later"
      ],
      "answer": "yesterday",
      "tts": "vakar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "dabar",
      "choices": [
        "now",
        "later",
        "today",
        "tomorrow"
      ],
      "answer": "now",
      "tts": "dabar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "valanda",
      "choices": [
        "hour",
        "minute",
        "day",
        "week"
      ],
      "answer": "hour",
      "tts": "valanda"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "šiandien"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "rytoj"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "vakar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "dabar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "valanda"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "šiandien",
      "choices": [
        "today",
        "tomorrow",
        "yesterday",
        "now"
      ],
      "answer": "today",
      "tts": "šiandien"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "rytoj",
      "choices": [
        "tomorrow",
        "today",
        "later",
        "yesterday"
      ],
      "answer": "tomorrow",
      "tts": "rytoj"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "vakar",
      "choices": [
        "yesterday",
        "today",
        "now",
        "later"
      ],
      "answer": "yesterday",
      "tts": "vakar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "dabar",
      "choices": [
        "now",
        "later",
        "today",
        "tomorrow"
      ],
      "answer": "now",
      "tts": "dabar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "valanda",
      "choices": [
        "hour",
        "minute",
        "day",
        "week"
      ],
      "answer": "hour",
      "tts": "valanda"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "šiandien"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "rytoj"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "vakar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "dabar"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "",
      "lt": "",
      "choices": [],
      "tts": "valanda"
    }
  ]
}